## Nayan A Thakkar

Address:-55 Elmcroft Crescent HA2 6HL,London,United Kingdom Mobile: +447367941135 | Email: <a href="mailto:nayanthakkar1910@gmail.com">nayanthakkar1910@gmail.com</a> LinkedIn: //www.linkedin.com/in/nayan-thakkar-67697a192

#### **Profile**

A Motivated, passionate and experienced Civil Engineer with knowledge about the Ground and Underground Work like Paver block, RCC Road, Drainage line, Strom Waterline. Moreover, residential, commercial building and Metro work experiences like Pile, Pile cap, Pier, Pier cap, footing, RCC Framework, brickwork, plasterwork, flooring, finishing and landscape work. All the projects finish under the budget with quality and ahead of schedule, Substantial knowledge and experience with environmentally sustainable construction.

# Work experience in United Kingdom UKTOP Architectural glazing & design Project Manager Barking Station, Fenchurch Station (£2M)

(July 2022 - Current)

#### Responsibility

- Time management- Used work breakdown structure to clearly define project activities and tasks for production and site installation work.
- Quality management- Ensured that all such as Schuco aluminum and Jansen steel door, windows and curtain wall products activities necessary to plan and implement a project were effective with respect to purpose of objective and its performance.
- Cost control- Meticulous planned budgets in consultation with key stakeholders.
- Risk management- Managed risk identification, mitigation and resolution to minimize impact on project success.

# Training in United Kingdom Golden Trees Limited Project Manager Fenchly (£ 1.5M)

(May 2022 - June 2022)

#### Responsibility

- Estimate and Quantity Surveyor: Calculated the quantity as per approved plan of each task like excavation, concrete work, brick work beam block and DPC and also calculate Laboure cost.
- As a site Manager to supervise a new build 3 flats works.
- In this site I have supervise the different type of work like Excavation work, Foundation concreter work, Brick work, DPC work, Beam and block work and water gas and drainage line work.

#### Hirani Engineers Limited

(April 2022 - May 2022)

# Structural Engineer

#### Responsibility

- As a junior assistant structural
- Analysis and Design a extension house, loft converter, and foundation in Tekla tedds software and generate the report.

#### Work experience in India

Maruti Project Project Manager

(July 2018 - August 2021)

Maruti L.axis Residential, Commercial and Bungalows Project (£8M)

#### Responsibility

- Estimate and Quantity Surveyor: Calculate the G+13 Story High rise building and eight bungalows Quantity and Equipment, Labour and Material cost for Excavation, PCC work, Footing, Pile foundation, Slab beam column Steel and concrete quantity also makes BBS, Brickwork, Plaster work, Flooring work, Underground water tank, and Landscaping work.
- As a Project Manager supervise G + 13 Story building and 8 bungalows.

- Execution on site of all site all the RCC frame elements like footing, pile, pile cap, plinth beams, retaining walls, beams, column, slab and RCC water tank underground and over ground.
- Also supervise brickwork, plasterwork, flooring, finishing and landscape work.
- Make the schedule for the following two weeks and assign the resource and every week arrange the meeting with stakeholders.
- Create advanced construction planning equipment planning and materials Quantity for whole projects.
- End of the day I make up a Daily Progress Report & check the work, Monitor the supervisor & labours.
- Last Date of the month: Prepare the Bill, documentation & presentation for the work.
- Creative, innovative, intersecting, public relation leadership & responsible person.

**K.D.** Corporation **Project Manager** Vastral Metro Station (£3M)

(May 2015 - June 2018)

#### Responsibility

- Estimate and Quantity Surveyor: Calculate the Quantity and Equipment, Labour and Material cost for Drainage line, Water line, Paver blocks, RCC Road, Pile, Pile cap, also all sub and Superstructure work
- Assistant civil engineer on several government projects and private and infrastructure projects.
- Executing various Executing of various structures of metro station like pile, pile cap, pier, pier cap, super structure and station brick work and finishing work. and industrial projects.
- Supervise structure like lift, staircase and foundation works of PEB.
- Maintaining records of various checklists of work done at site.
- Record of extra items at site and get it approved from the client.
- Verify measurement of sub-contractor for the process of bill.
- Working with clients, contractors, local authorities and government officers on various renovation and new build projects.

# Shivam Engineering Classes

(June 2012- June-2020)

#### **Assistant Professor**

- Teaching assistants teach more than 10 subjects including Estimating, structure design, construction management and Building surveyor and many more.
- Teaching more than 300 students with passing rate of 95 percent.
- Delivered learning support on remote basic through zoom and Google classroom.
- Helped students to achieve target grades through continuous curriculum support and motivation.

#### **Education**

# **Kingston University, London, United Kingdom** MSc Structural Design and Construction Management with Sustainability (Grade 2:2)

(Sept 2021- Sept 2022)

Core Modules:

- Management of project Risk, quality and Safety
- Estimating, Tendering and Procurement
- Structure Design in Concrete and steel
- Sustainable Construction and substructure Design
- Dissertation: Post-Tensioned Floor Using RAPT

### Gujarat Technological University, Gujarat India

(May 2012 - June 2015)

Bachelor of Civil Engineering GPA - 2.9/4.0

# **Key Skills**

- Computer Skill: AutoCAD 2D, PPM Concepts, STAAD Pro, ETABS, Tekla Tedds, MS project, Microsoft office, Outlook, QuickBooks, Logical Estimating software, Bluebeam
- Soft Skill: Team Working, Communication, Critical thinking, Leadership
- Language: English, Hindi, Gujarati.
- CSCS Card (AQP).

# **Interests & hobbies**

- Structure Analysis
- Planning
- Watching innovation new Video

- Like to do Photography in my leisure time.
- I am interested in playing and watching team games like cricket.

# REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST